Gold Grotter, the King of the Pirates, attained every treasure that the world had to offer.
Smiling, even as he stood upon the scaffold, he issued a challenge to the world.
You want my treasure? You can have it.
I left everything I gathered together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
Now those who dare to dream hoist their flags and sail into the Great Pirate Era.
It's time for a long time.
One, two, three, shine, you! We'll call!
We'll be right back to the Break of Romance Love.
We'll be right back to the Slip from the Jump Start.
We'll be right back to the world.
We'll be right back.
私たちのルール
心配なんて床吹かぜ
Time of peace 一番遠い
夢見る心は超でかい
冷めないことが大事
止まらない
夜明けが遅くでじれた
1 2 3 Shine!
We go!
止まれない 心の太陽 絆タイム
1,2,3,Shine!
We go!
It's been two whole years since Monkey's crew came here.
Seems like only yesterday.
Yeah.
We haven't changed, but I bet they've all grown up.
Can't wait to see.
Well, I wouldn't get ahead of myself.
For all we know, they might not even make it here.
They're not small fries anymore, thanks to their captain.
The whole world is after them.
Well...
I didn't think you'd be the first.
Oh, yeah?
Nobody else has shown up?
Well, damn.
Guess they got lost.
The beginning of the new chapter.
The Straw Hats reunited.
Did you hear? They relocated Navy HQ.
Oh? Did they now?
Yeah.
They traded locations with the branch called G1.
That moved them to the other side of the Red Line.
Their new Fleet Admiral's a lot more cocky than Sengoku was.
Move right into the Four Emperor's territory.
He's not afraid to stare down the toughest pirates in the world.
On the upside, that keeps him out of our business.
But on the downside, we've got a lot more criminals running around
and nobody to stop them if things get ugly.
Oh.
It did seem like there were an awful lot of thugs compared to two years ago.
Hey, did you catch this?
Yeah, it's a shocker, huh?
I had to do a double take, but it looks like the Straw Hats are back after all.
I never heard word of them dying or anything, but two years is a long time for anyone to just disappear like that.
Either way, looks like they're recruiting some new members.
This is a good place for it.
If you made it here, that means you survived the first half of the Grand Line and those guys keep pouring in.
His crew's pretty small.
Makes sense that he'd want to pick up some more before heading to the new world.
That sounds like fun to me.
I'd make a great straw hat, right?
Fat chance.
There's guys with 100 million berry bounties all over the place here.
What would they want with a chump like you?
That's cruel, man.
Hey Grandpa, how about some drinks and some food? Give me everything you got.
Yes, sir.
Hey, I think that's them.I know that's them.
Just look.
He's got a straw hat.It's gotta be.
It's the first half of the Grand Line.
Oh my god, they're getting shit, they're getting shit, they're getting shit, they're getting shit.
Oh come on, bro.There's gotta be something you can do.
Like what?We're sold out.This is the Soul King world tour!
world tour. You can't waltz up and buy tickets when the show is about to start. This is the
final concert of the tour, too. Can't you hear them? The crowd is ready to rock!
Hey, manager. Let's make this the greatest show of my afterlife. Well, of course, of course. Now
would be the time. Your TDs are at the height of their sales. In fact, we just broke a million.
You certainly earned your title as the King of Soul. Just listen to those fans chanting your name.
I can dig it, boss man. But one thing before the concert. I got something heavy to lay on you.
I'm all ears, friend.
Come on, baby!
I love you down to my heart!
我不brar.
Born to be well.
I'm locked to my soul, cause the ladies love my hustle, baby.
It's no mystery, just rock with me.
And you'll see why I'm the king.
I'm gonna wring his sorry neck bone.
How selfish can he be?
Hey, grab me a transponder, snail.
I'm not gonna let you walk all over me, Brooke.
Today is a reunion, an anniversary, and a celebration!
I never thought I'd miss this place so much, but I sure am glad to be back.
Women! Real women!
No stubble, no hairy legs, no giant chins, just honest to goodness beautiful girls!
How I've longed for your delicate features.
Your soft skin, to hear the intoxicating words resting on your sweet lips.
VIVA SAMODI!
I NEED LADIES!
VIVA SAMODIES!
I hope not!
Thanks for the ride and say hi to Eva, but go away.
What's up, ladies?
I'm fresh out of hell and looking for a good time!
Like they say, if a boy picks on a girl, that means he has a crush on her.
Oh, I know. Happens to me all the time.
Love is patient, Sanji! We'll wait! We know you'll come back!
I'm on my way, Nami Suwan! Robin, my love!
What's the matter? Can't read? Or are you just stupid?
I know preschoolers with higher bounties than that.
How about you check that poster again? If your bounty is under 70 million, then we don't want you.
So why don't you take your weak ass back to pirate daycare?
If that's all you're worth, it's a wonder you made it this far.
Bastard!
Now scram! I'm the thun of Dragon the Revolutionary. I ain't got time for this.
We're the chosen ones, boyo. No chumps are gonna run with this crew.
We're in a league of our own. If you can't get with us, you better get the hell out of our way.
Too late.
That's rough. Serral had his fears. Of course he is. He's a legend.
What's the count, Frankie? How many recruits we got?
About a hundred last time I checked. Three whole crews joined up along with ten guys running solo.
They've got some nice bounties, too.
I know two of them. A pair of high profile rookies joined at the same time.
Wet-haired caribou and blood splatter coribou. They love killing marines.
Brothers and captains worth $210 million and $190 million.
Now they answer to us.
And there's more where they came from.
Hey! Bring another round!
Yes, sir.
Better make it quick.
I see you sitting alone over there, missy.
If you want to have a good time, why don't you party with us?
She's a real looker, ain't she?
Hey! Sister! I'm talking to you!
Lady, did you hear him?
I'll pass.
I'm here waiting for a friend.
This is about to get ugly.
Listen, I would not turn that man down.
You realize that straw hat Luffy, right?
Yeah, the same straw hat that burst into Marineford and went head-to-head with the Navy Admirals.
He's nuts!
Waiting for a friend? Captain Luffy is a star, baby.
Your friend would probably piss his pants if he saw him.
Come drink with some real men.
I'm only gonna say this once.
You can take your offer and shove it, cause I'm way out of your league.
What?
You understand?
Mr...
Whoever you are?
Jason
I'm a would-
I'm Straw Hat Luffy, you wint.
Hey, come on. Say you're sorry. Hurry!
Nobody disrespects me.
Let me handle this.
Har har. You think you're real cute, don't you?
I'll make this super simple, okay?
Either you come drink with Captain Luffy, or you die.
For your info, I have a bounty myself.
I'm the Straw Hat's navigator, Nami.
You scared yet?
Special attack, Green Star?
Devil!
Huh?
Whoa, what the hell?
Captain, save me!
Save myself!
Come on!
A giant plant? Where'd that come from?
Hey there, beautiful.
Can I buy you a drink?
Ahem.
Ah!
Ah! Look at you!
Those muscles! And that hair!
You tough guy! You look great! I missed you!
Ah, thanks. Uh, you're, uh, your hair looks nice, too!
That hot girl was waiting for that pencil-nosed geek.
What does he have to week out?
New special move, huh?
Yeah, they come from seeds called Pop Greens.
Needless to say, I wasn't just sitting around on my tail these past two years.
It's a new me!
I'm not part of the weakling trio with you and Chopper anymore.
That means no more running and hiding. I'm a real warrior now!
Uh, hey, dude! If you did this, could you undo it?
What the?! Sniper King?! But how?!
Usopp, forget about them!
Let's get out of here. There's something we need to talk about.
You stop right there!
Lupi?!
Ignore him!
Ma'am, you haven't paid your tab yet!
Keep the change!
Crap! They're making fools of us!
Get them down now!
Son of a...
Huh?
Um, guys? What are those weird bubble things?
Uh-uh.
I have a feeling this ain't going to be pretty.
Ah!
What the hell's going on here?
Yeah, so I picked up some new special moves myself.
You show off. Can't you let me be cool for once?
Uh-uh.
Who do they think they are?
Hunt those bastards down and murder them.
I have a report, sir, from Saba Odi Archipelago.
What?
You say the Straw Hats are back?
Yes, sir.
Word is that they're recruiting new crew members before they head to the new world.
Had a feeling Straw Hat was still alive.
Inform headquarters of this immediately.
Send in as many backup units as we can spare and begin a search of the entire archipelago.
Sir!
I think I shook them off.
Brooke is holding a concert and the Straw Hats are looking for new recruits?
Goodness.
I've been gone for too long.
Soul King does have a nice ring to it, though.
Well, I'll be damned.
Not a scratch on the whole ship.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sonny.
We'll be sailing off soon.
I almost forgot.
The foots dolls here are great.
I hope everyone's okay.
I sure do miss them.
Whoa!
I wonder if they're Кол Okay.
I want the big one!
Whoa!
Hey! Are you alright? Hey!
Why did he do that? He just shot her out of the blue!
That's awful!
Come on! We'll get a doctor!
You! What is wrong with you?
She didn't do a damn thing to deserve that!
Ugh, I thought you were someone else. I said sorry.
So, here's the deal. I'm looking for some punks who crossed me and made a run for it.
A red-haired woman and a guy with a long nose.
So you just shot her? That's normal for you?
This won't end well. Strawhead's a monster.
Eh? You wanna fight about it? Cause I got plenty more bullets.
Your choice, pal.
Don't blame me. Blame your nose.
Hey! We'll get some help. Stay with me.
Find those punks now, or I'll shoot you too!
We got a reputation to uphold here! We gotta show this place who's boss!
Who's boss?!
Oops. Didn't see you there. Sorry about that. See ya!
See ya!
That guy's insane. Either that, or he doesn't know who Strawhead is.
He's a dead man either way.
Get back here!
Huh?
A crew of fake Straw Hat Pirates is formed, taking advantage of the disappearance of the real Straw Hats.
Luffy, in disguise, crosses paths with the fake Luffy, who causes a scene in the middle of Saba-Ori.
Unaware of who he's facing, the imposter finds himself on the receiving end of a mysterious power.
On the next, One Piece, an explosive situation. Luffy vs. Fake Luffy, I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Now, our three entered the book series.
One Piece Manê!
W sentinel from The Fur Panda News group on Son of the Twinkle Beach
Halloween One Piece are in the King of the Pirates.
Hello friends andации are taking advantage of one piece!